metromasti.com 2011-06-23

# Entertainment, Latest News Portal

Welcome to metromasti.com. We value your privacy, and want you to know what information we collect and what we do with it.

From time to time, we may make changes to this Policy. We will endeavor to post the changes before they become effective. The effective date of the most recent version of the privacy policy will appear at the top of this page. This consumer privacy policy applies to any information we collect or receive about you, from any source.

**WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We have several areas where members can submit information to us, and we also have features that automatically collect information from our members and other users.

**INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO US.**

We have certain areas where we ask you to provide information to us:

* Registration. You may register with us to use some of our member only features on our site. We may also offer the option for you to register with us or sign up for our mailing list without having to use any other product or service. During registration, you provide your "contact information" (which identifies you and how we can contact you, such as your name and email address) as well as certain demographic information (which describes certain information about you, such as your country of residence). You may be asked to enter a e-mail address and password. We may also ask you to provide additional information about your music preferences, so that we can cater to those preferences.

* In order to keep our members informed about the operation of our services, we will send e-mails and announcements that are needed for the proper functioning and administration of our site and subscription service. For additional information about our site, services and offers, we give our members the option of joining our mailing list. We also allow you to choose whether to receive mails from partners and sponsors that we think will be of interest to you. Each marketing e-mail from us will come with instructions on how to unsubscribe from our mailing list.

* Communications with Us. We have features where you can submit information to us (such as when contacting us with a question or problem related to the service). We will retain your emails and other information you submit to us for our internal purposes, and to help us to serve you better.

* Communications with Friends. Our site may also have certain features that allow you to send information to others (such as via a "Tell a Friend", "Mail a song"). We will use the contact information you enter for your friends only to send the email, and then we will delete it from our system.

* Interactive Features. We also may offer interactive features, such as message boards, chat rooms, etc. Note that all personal information you send or post via such features becomes public information, and we are not responsible for any information you choose to make public (including any online identifier, such as an email address, instant messenger name or member name). We may store such information in an aggregate form but we will not file or retain such information on a personal basis. We may monitor such traffic via electronic software or personnel but only to check for obscenity, defamation or other types of abusive language, which we reserve the right to remove at any time.

* Surveys. We may occasionally ask members to participate in surveys. Such surveys will be voluntary. They are intended to improve your member experience and any information you provide we may associate with your member name for future use. Any personal information collected will be used only by us unless we specify otherwise, although we may share aggregate survey result information with others.

**AUTOMATIC DATA COLLECTION**

Cookies. We use a software technology called "cookies" for several purposes, depending on the type of cookie employed. Within MetroMasti.com, we use what are commonly called "session" cookies, meaning that they only last as long as you are online. We use these cookies to identify you as a valid subscriber so that we can deliver music to you, to ensure that no one else can sign on simultaneously with your account from another computer and to help us personalize your service experience based on your registration preferences (such as genre). We may also use session cookies to help us facilitate any promotions or surveys that we provide. As part of the sign-in process, we may also use what are commonly called "persistent" cookies which stay with you after your session is over and you are offline. We only use these cookies in connection with a sign-in feature that allows you to save your member name and password so that the next time you sign in, these fields will be prepopulated for you. This cookie is only offered in conjunction with certain Affiliate Sites that choose to make it available and it can only be activated if you select that option during your sign-in. If you select this option you can always deselect it each time you sign-in.

Other. In order to personalize our service for your enjoyment and to monitor and improve the performance of our technology, we do collect/capture other data such as a member's searches (such as their search criteria and results) and the music they listened to. We only share search history or music usage data on an aggregate basis.

For our internal purposes, we gather information such as date, time, connection speed and IP address of all visitors to our site. We keep this information simply for our internal security audit log, trend analysis, and system administration.

**Third Party Advertising**

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

**WITH WHOM WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION**

We do not share your personally identifiable information with other companies, apart from those acting as our agents in providing our service to you, all of which agree to use it only for that purpose and to keep the information secure and confidential. Also, entities into which our company is merged, or to which our assets, site or operations have been transferred, will be able to use your personal information under the terms of this privacy policy. We will also disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena or other legal obligation, in response to a law enforcement agency's request, or in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property. You should also be aware that courts of equity, such as U.S. Bankruptcy Courts, may have the authority under certain circumstances to permit your information to be shared or transferred to third parties without your permission. 

We may share (provide and receive) with others certain aggregate service information, which is not personally identifiable. This information may include usage and demographic data, but it will not include personal information (such as your email address). We may use aggregate demographic information about our audience in order to improve our service, for marketing purposes and/or industry reporting purposes.

We partner with third-party advertising companies to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. These companies may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information [not including your name, address, email address or telephone number] during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. 

**SECURITY**

MetroMasti.com endeavors to protect the security of your personal information and your choices for its intended use. We use secure SSL technology to protect the transmission of sensitive information such as your registration, login, and credit card information.

We store your personal information on a secure server, and use special procedures designed to protect the information we collect from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction.

**LINKS**

We may display links to other sites within MetroMasti.com. We are not responsible for those other sites, their privacy policies or how they treat information about their members. We advise you to check their privacy policies to find out how they are treating your personal information.

We use Google and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

*Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.

*Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

*Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**THIRD PARTY COOKIES**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with MetroMasti.com , please write to contactus@srisoftsystems.com
